In the arena of liberty, the wise men are being used as battle axes in the hands of God,
cutting down demonic chains that have held the people in bondage,
setting them free at the mention of Jesus' name.
Jesus is the sinners only Saviour.
What you are watching is the reality that Jesus lives and never said "goodbye".
Watch as Wise Man Daniel moves along this row, and the reaction of this young man,
as he encounters the Wise Man.
He doesn't want to look at the Wise Man's face, and has become suddenly uncomfortable,
as the Holy Spirit is at work exposing the darkness in his life.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Why are you touching the veil?
Who are you?
Don’t touch the veil.
Fire! Come out and speak out you demon!
Speak out, who are you!?
I said I am Morpheus!
And who else apart from Morpheus?
Leo!
Leave him!
Can you open your eyes? Do you know where you are?
Open your eyes! Say now where you are! Open your eyes!
Stand up and talk, you demon.
Stand up!
You want this boy to destroy the world?
No – not what our master has so far acquired.
You said you were Morpheus?
Yes.
Who is the next person?
Leo. I am a big cat.
You are a big cat?
The lion.
A lion.
Who else again?
I said Adder.
Adder?
It is a relative of a viper.
A relative of the viper?
Yes.
We are three beings in him because this guy is too strong,
too powerful and too supreme in the spirit realm.
You might be seeing him as a little, small, simple and humble boy
but in the spirit realm, when he opens his mouth to praise God or pray,
our kingdoms are threatened heavily.
Every secret in this world is revealed.
That is why we came in him to silence his destiny
but all the prayers of his beloved mother keep on saving him all the time. You see?
I don’t know what is making me say this but I am under an influence I cannot fathom.
It is making me confess; I will say it.
Before...
Our master will kill me but I cannot control myself.
Who is the master that sent you?
Please don’t make me say his name.
Speak out! Come on - speak out!
It’s Baphomet. He is a pagan god for whom the Righteous One closed all sacrifice
and worship that was supposed to be made in the open.
The Righteous One came to this world and destroyed it
and now our master only receives his praises and sacrifice through this world's music.
I am telling you. This boy is a very good singer.
You say he is what?
He is multi-talented.
He is good in arts, science; he is good in anything.
Music, basketball, you name it.
Our master saw that his soul was only answering to the Righteous One.
His soul yearns for the Righteous One.
My master is the one that people in the music industry of this world worship.
OK. You said that all the "openings" through which he receives sacrifices
were blocked by the Righteous One.
Yes.
And that they devised another means...
Through music!
Does it mean your demonic kingdom rules through worldly music?
Yes!
You may know us with different names.
Like what?
Above all we have the satan’s church, we have the Illuminati,
we have the AMORC Rosicrucian Order and the Ku Klux Klan.
And you say you people operate through the music?
Yes!
Can you explain how you operate through the music?
We do our signs like this.
Take it easy. What is the first one? The first sign...
Come on! Show the first sign. What is the first sign?
The first one.
Is it how you show the first sign?
Yes!
What does it represent?
It is a way of rendering glory, power, adoration and above all, loyalty,
to the master, meaning, “I have only one master”.
Of which kingdom - kingdom of light or darkness?
When I mention the pagan gods, we rule the celestial, atmosphere, land
and the seas, more especially darkness.
Darkness?
Yes.
When they were about to give birth to this soul, we killed four of his initial siblings ahead of him.
His mother was known to be barren.
He came and my master sent us to kill him.
On that day, that very night in the hospital, somewhere in Imo State...
oh no, not Imo State, but somewhere in the Ibo land. It is what we call "Arondisog".
Yes, I remember vividly well.
We came that night to take him out of the womb and the Righteous One intervened.
He cut us off. We were paralysed; we couldn’t kill him.
He was born and our master vowed that we – Leo, Morpheus and Adder -
must make sure that this soul dies before he is eight years old.
We tried all means but he survived because of the fervent prayers of his mother.
We tried other ways to kill him; we caused accidents and catastrophes, you name it.
We tried but his mother’s prayers and the heartbeat of this soul, his heart...
Just like you say in the Bible, “David is a man after God’s heart”. That is true.
You said what?
I said, I did not stutter...
I said just like in the Bible - "David is a man after God's heart".
This soul is also a man after God’s heart.
He doesn’t love vanity; he doesn’t love material things.
He only has love for humans, even for those he doesn’t know.
As long as he knows that person is in need, he is willing to help.
He is willing to share anything he has.
OK, can you tell us how you rule the world through worldly music? How?
I said, when we sing, we twist the mind and the soul of the human body
to have 100% lust for vanity, music, sex and anything that is sinful.
Such soul can never – as we are doing to this soul – read the Word of God.
They can never pray fervently or visit the house of God steadily.
You will always...
Please!
You want to do what?
The soul will always look for beer parlours, clubs, prostitution houses, you name it.
Anything that involves sin but does not involve the Righteous One.
Through this music you lure human souls into the things that involve sins.
Yes.
Does it mean that you possess these worldly songs?
Before these worldly songs are released, our worshippers render our own prayers.
When they offer the prayer - is it physically or spiritually?
It is always in the secret chamber, undisclosed to man.
Undisclosed to man?
Yes.
Where is that secret chamber located?
They are around everywhere in this world.
Everywhere?
We are everywhere.
We own this world but the Righteous One wants to take it from our master.
The Righteous One wants to take this evil kingdom from your master?
Yes.
You said anytime a music is released, you people offer prayer in your secret chamber.
Can you answer me!
You say what?
You pray?
Yes.
When you offer a prayer, what does that prayer do to the music, before it is released?
It’s not just ordinary prayers. It’s like an incantation.
Like an incantation?
Yes.
Do you know that language?
I cannot disclose such language.
Answer - do you know the language?
It is not for us to say; it is for the worshippers to say.
It is worshippers that say it?
The language is just like a programme. It programmes us; it gives us license.
To do what?
To manifest into the human.
Let's say that somebody is listening to some of the music you have possessed;
what would happen to that person as he is listening to the song?
What would you do?
For instance, by merely listening to the music, we don’t have full license into you
until you use a catalyst that will speed up the reaction.
What is the catalyst that speeds up the reaction?
You can talk about drinks, morphine, heroin, cocaine or marijuana -
anything that will open the mind and make the gateway to the mind free,
that will send the Spirit of God away from the gateway of the mind.
Before that, we tried so many ways to initiate this soul.
As of 2009/2010 after his service as a copper,
he came in contact with our full member who was tattooed on his body.
There were tattoos?
Our member who was tattooed from the shoulder region to the stomach.
He saw our symbol which is the eye you see on a dollar bill,
just like in the pyramids in the days of old.
When he met with your full member what happened to him?
He was supposed to be the right-hand man to welcome Damien into this world.
Who is Damien?
Damien is popularly known in this world. His mark is 666.
Yes.
How many people have you possessed through music in this world?
They are billions, zillions, an uncountable amount.
Uncountable?
Uncountable.
What is happening to their lifestyles now?
When they go to church, they hear God’s Word
and we are being forced to run outside and wait for them.
When they come out, because of their habit which is the catalyst, we come back.
What do you do to their lives when you come back?
We make it even worse than before; we tarnish everything.
You said that those who listen to your worldly music which you possess,
they don't have the time for God.
Yes!
How do you distinguish those people from real children of God?
It’s simple. We know by the catalyst they take. Alcohol is also a catalyst.
What is the difference between those people and the children of God?
Those people are like vessels for us; vessels that we possess.
Those who take this catalyst?
Yes.
They are vessels.
Can you people possess the children of God through this worldly music? Is it possible?
No, because they don’t use the catalysts.
The catalyst facilitates your going inside?
Yes.
It is only those who use...
It is our license.
It is your license?
Yes - to enter.
To enter?
Yes.
How did you enter this body? There must be a means. Is it through a catalyst?
How did you possess this body?
He was introduced to that catalyst when he was in school.
His first cousin who is a cultist tried to initiate him.
He didn’t but he succeeded in giving him the catalyst.
This very soul, being the only one in that zone and far away from the Righteous One,
took that catalyst as his daily bread. He cannot eat, sleep or rest without having it.
That is how we came into possession of him.
Before, we could only cause havoc and harm his way.
We stripped him off of his work in oil companies that he was supposed to have.
We stripped him of his talents as a computer engineer.
We made him...
OK, listen. Can you mention the talents this boy has that made you want to destroy him?
What are the talents? Mention them one by one. The first one?
He’s good at music; he’s good in praises.
He started worshipping God from the children’s choir, to the teenage choir, to the adult choir,
until when he got into university and the catalyst was introduced.
OK.
We made him...
Listen. From the primary school to the secondary school level he was closer to God?
Yes.
But when they introduced the catalyst to him - you entered.
And you manipulated him
Yes.
Can you show us the second sign you were trying to demonstrate?
Second sign!
What does it imply?
It implies Damien’s mark.
Does it mean that some humans beings possess these signs and marks you are talking about?
No. They don’t just possess the sign. They feel it is just like a freestyle sign,
like you do in music but it simply says, “Damien, I am your vessel to possess.
I am your soul to claim”.
OK.
Once again. You said you people were three dwelling in this body.
Yes.
The first person?
His name is Morpheus.
Second person?
Which is Leo!
The third person?
Adder!
Morpheus, Leo, and Adder; you say you operate like a lion, cat...
... and the god of dreams.
And the...?
The god of dreams!
What do you mean by the god of dreams?
The god of dreams is the one who puts the human mind in a trance, whether drugged, high or normal.
OK, right now; you Morpheus, you Leo, you Adder, that manifest in a form of a lion, cat,
or wicked god of dreams - it is time to leave this body.
Jesus wants you out right now.
Please, we are begging you. Please, do not remove...
Come out!
Fire!
Hey - you are going.
This one will destroy our works.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Inside your head.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus!
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Lord. You are free. Rise up!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
This light is too bright.
Come.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
How are you?
Good day, sir.
Good day.
Do you remember what happened to you?
Why am I sweating?
Are you sweating?
Yes.
What made you to be sweating?
I don't know.
What happened to you?
How did I get here?
How did you...
I was about to ask you because I am surprised that you are here. How come you are here?
I don’t know these people.
You don't know which people?
Who brought me here?
It must be a bad dream. What happened?
How did I get here?
I was supposed to ask you. I'm asking you too. I'm surprised to see you here.
I can’t remember anything.
Come.
It all calls for joy. OK?
OK.
But you just said something now. Do you remember what you said?
I said, "How did I get here?"
Is that all you said?
You didn't say anything else?
I remember the last one. I asked if this was a bad dream or something.
OK. Maybe I should remind you what you said?
Yes.
You said you were Morpheus...
Me?
Yes.
Sorry, you mistook me for someone else.
My name is Ochia Innocent Oluchi Chidozie.
OK. It's a pleasure to meet you.
OK, it’s a pleasure, sir.
You said you were Adder.
Adder?
I do not understand.
I don’t know who is Adder, please.
You said you were Leo.
Leo?
Yes.
No. How can I be Leo?
You said you manifest as a lion.
As a lion?
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Sir, if you look at me physically, I am a human being.
I don’t have claws, teeth, or fangs like a lion.
Not only that. You said that you manifest as a big cat.
Oh my God.
Big cat, sir – maybe you are mistaking me for someone else.
And also like a viper.
No, sir. It’s not me.
It is a clear proof that that demon that tormented your career and life is out.
OK?
Give thanks to God.
Praise be to God.
Oh, this is a house of...
Set Free in Jesus' Name
What happened to you?
I never knew I was in the House of God.
You never knew you were in the House of God? You discovered it now?
Yes. I thought it was a theatre, maybe showbiz…
No. This is a House of God.
Stand up.
Thank You, Jesus!
I am free!
TESTIMONY TIME
Citizens of Heaven - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ochia Innocent Oluchi Chidozie. I am from Imo State, Nigeria.
I come from a family of four; I am the firstborn.
I was a member of the church and in the children's choir
from when I was a child and then I was in the teenage choir.
I gained admission into university, where I then met my cousin who was an occultist.
He initiated me into the acts of drugs, smoking, drinking, and everything.
After I was initiated, I stopped everything that had to do with music -
the choir, the church – I stayed away from the church.
I loved the new me that I was introduced to.
OK. You said that you were introduced to drugs.
Can you tell us the drugs that you were introduced to
and how much of these drugs you were taking.
I was introduced to marijuana, morphine, and other types of drugs.
How much of these were you taking on a daily basis?
On a daily basis, I could pop three pills of a drug and mix it with another.
I would also smoke a bag of marijuana, in order to feel stronger and high.
In the process of taking these drugs, I discovered that I hated the world; I was anti-social.
If people would come around me, I would block my ears with earpieces and listen to worldly music.
I would not pay attention to what people were saying.
Before this time you were growing up in the church, you were in the choir, you were a Christian.
As you were growing up, it was these drugs you were introduced to,
that actually took you away from God.
Yes. Those drugs blotted out everything that had to do with God within me.
It was as if they erased it from my memory and from my body.
I got joy out of taking drugs.
It was as if it was a tribute I had to do for something that was inside of me -
to manifest and possess me.
I didn't know.
Yes, I started listening to all kinds of worldly music.
I never had...
If you played any Christian music around me, I would simply walk out and not want to be around it.
I wouldn’t download Christian music on my phone – only worldly music.
As I was introduced to drugs and was taking them every day,
I noticed that I had several encounters but I never knew what it was.
I took it as if it was a part of my day-to-day activities.
I went for service and I came back to reimburse myself.
I needed to get more money in order to complete my service.
I served in Niger State and I didn’t see any means of getting money there,
so I went back to my parents to get more money.
When I got home, they told me that they couldn’t give me the money immediately.
They said that I was looking thin – as though I hadn’t eaten.
They said that I should stay home and eat well, before going back.
I would still sneak out and continue my bad habits – smoking and drinking.
Then it occurred to me...
I went to a special bar where people would drink and at the back, they’d smoke.
I went there, isolated myself from the crowd and was smoking as usual.
I played my music loud.
Three beings then manifested.
They were three people that I did not know.
I hadn’t seen them before.
I was just surprised.
They came exactly to where I was and sat down in a circle.
One was directly facing me – he was dark in complexion.
The other two were at my side.
I didn’t converse with them because I had joy in what I was doing.
I had love for what I was doing.
I was saying in my head that any song I hear, I could make it and say it exactly,
I wished I could be a popular musician.
I wanted to be like that.
The one directly facing me uttered that he could hear my thoughts,
that he could hear everything I said.
I was stunned. I pointed to myself and asked, “Are you referring to me?”
In my mind, that was what I said because I wanted to be sure that he was talking to me.
He said, “Yes” and pointed towards me, “I was talking to you”.
I didn’t want to speak in English or orally.
I wanted to be sure that he wasn’t using any gimmicks or is a second-class magician.
I asked, “What was I saying?”
He said, “You said, ‘I want to be famous, like a rap star’.”
He said, “It comes at a price”.
I said in my head, “What is this price?
If it involves bloodshed, I am not going to partake in it”.
He said that it didn’t involve bloodshed but there was an initiation, a ritual I had to do.
I told him to show me the ritual, that I would do it.
I never spoke aloud to them; they were reading my every thought.
It was as if the gateway of my mind was open for them to see what was going on inside there.
They read my every thought.
He told me that in order for me to continue the procedure, I had to follow some instructions.
I said he should tell me the instructions.
He then removed his clothes.
I was baffled. I was scared, instantly because of what I saw.
I had never seen such a tattoo before, on any human being.
He was tattooed from the neck down to his stomach.
There was a pyramid with an eye inside it.
It was the same tattoo all around; there was no other tattoo.
The same tattoo was repeated all over his body.
He stopped speaking to me orally and started speaking through his mind.
He said I should follow the procedure - that I should look at the tattoo and lust after it,
as if I was being seduced by a lady.
He said that was the procedure.
I said, “OK”.
He stretched forth his arm and I started lusting after the tattoo on his arm.
When it got to his neck, I noticed that he started moaning as if someone was making love to him.
I asked, “What am I doing? This is a man. I’m not gay. Why should I lust after a man?"
I stood up and left the circle.
He shouted orally to me, “You are going to die in four days!”
I didn’t complete the initiation.
When I went home, in my dreams, before those four days elapsed,
I kept seeing a being manifesting with a face of somebody I knew.
He told me, “You are a mut. When we call you, you run.
When we want you to do something, you run away.
You don’t want to finish it”.
He said that they were not happy with me
and that I’d never be successful until I finished the initiation.
He said that I’d never be the rap star I wanted to be until I finished that initiation.
I took it as a mere dream; I didn’t take it seriously.
After the four days elapsed, I went back to a different spot and was smoking and drinking as usual.
When I was listening to the worldly music, the voices became clearer.
I was able to decipher song lyrics, as if they were sent straight to me.
They would tell me what to do, how to dress and how to manipulate.
They put me in a trance.
When I entered that trance, I saw myself walking normally along a footpath;
I didn’t know that I was walking in the middle of a highway.
The cars were too scared to hit me – I didn’t know what caused that.
People who were near to me were screaming, “What is wrong with you? You are on the highway!"
I didn’t answer them.
My life became stagnant.
I wasn’t going forwards or backwards, I just stayed where I was.
If I submitted my CV, there would be no phone call for a job.
Anything I did, there was no way.
When I tried to go for projects, to study external courses in computer,
I ended up having white elephant projects – I ended up running away.
I ended up being in rehab and everything about me was messed up.
Immediately after that encounter, any time you listened to this worldly music
you would be hearing a voice
that would be telling you exactly what to do, how to dress, how to behave.
Can you just give us an example of what that voice was telling you to do?
The voice told me the first day I started hearing it, that I was an ace in the hood,
that nobody could manipulate me
and that if I doubted it, I should do the instructions and see what would happen.
He told me that there were baggy jeans that my uncle sent me from Germany,
which is one of a kind and not available anywhere, that I should press the logo of an ace on them
and that I should walk around dressed like a gangster in any neighbourhood
and that I would see what would happen.
I obeyed the voice. I went and did exactly as instructed.
I customized the jeans and dressed up like that.
I walked into dangerous neighbourhoods, even in the North, where people were armed with guns.
I was like a fearless lion.
When I entered, they all gave way.
Even people who were asking who I was wanted to know me,
they would want to stop me but I knew what to say to them and they would just give way.
They wouldn’t stop me; I’d have my way.
If I needed something and had no money, I would open my mouth and say, "This is what I want"
and they would give it to me.
When I was in that hood, when I sang under the influence of that evil spirit,
everybody would go into a trance.
Some of them who could not stand the trance would run away,
while some would end up sleeping as if they were lifeless.
They would not know themselves.
I did whatever I wanted to do and walked away.
The life I was living under the influence of that voice was a terrible life - a very dangerous one.
Anyone who was a Christian could sense that there was a force on me
because I would look at you as if I wanted to devour you, as if you were a prey.
It was as if I was ready to jump on you and kill you.
I didn’t like official things like suits or anything corporate.
I didn’t have any of them.
I didn’t have any zeal for them.
I loved anything that had to do with gangsters, different ugly signs, skulls
and all kinds of things that portrayed the evil realm.
I loved it so much.
I would feel this ego in me that would grow and made me walk as if I was a demi-god in society.
Nobody would mess with me. Everybody was scared of me. Everybody is afraid of me.
Even those who were strong enough to test me,
I would know what to say to them and they would just walk away.
I went to rehab on two occasions.
On the first occasion, I went for three months.
When I came out, I thought it was all over.
The voice came back and told me not to worry, that I was taking much before
that this time, I should take a little.
That If I took a little, it would be OK, that I would not be taken back there.
I obeyed the voice and when I started to obey the voice, the same spirit came back and possessed me.
This time around, I caused a catastrophe at home:
I scattered my room, punctured my ceiling, scattered my dad’s car and never said, "Sorry".
I was even feeling proud that what I was doing was right.
Then I was sent back to rehab for another six months.
So, altogether, it was nine months I spent in rehab.
When I came out of rehab, I thought it was all over.
I never knew that the stigma was still there and that evil spirit that was talking to me.
I was hearing this voice clearly.
It was telling me, “See, you are not moving forward, there is no work; you are only at home.
Why are you sitting down at home? Go and smoke and forget your problems
and you will see, everything will be fine".
I went back to it and started to see the manifestations again.
I enjoyed it and reasoned that it was better to manifest than to be idle.
When I was taking those drugs, I had a hundred percent hatred for the Word of God.
I could not open the Bible for five minutes.
If I opened it, it was as if I was looking through pages; nothing would enter.
I could not pray at all. My prayer life was really low.
I never fasted, paid tithes or offering. I hated everything about that.
I was absent...
Even on the Sabbath day, the day which is holy for God, I never attended church.
I preferred staying at home, washing my clothes and doing other things.
That was the day I set out to wash my clothes.
I didn’t wash clothes on any other day except on the Sabbath day.
How did you come to be in the Synagogue Church of all Nations?
I was informed by my parents that their older sister was delivered at The SCOAN.
We didn’t have this station at home, we watched DSTV.
I didn’t know about Emmanuel TV.
They told me that my auntie was delivered but they couldn’t go, so I should go to represent them.
I said OK since it was just one day. I could go and come back.
I rushed down with a few things and came down.
When I came to The SCOAN, it was a Saturday deliverance service.
I was feeling very uncomfortable.
I was wondering where I could go and smoke.
I had never watched Emmanuel TV. I never knew what was happening here.
I just thought it was going to be like a normal day church service.
When the Wise Man prayed for me, it was as if fire was burning me.
It was so hot, I couldn’t stand because everything about me was inflamed.
I couldn’t fathom the force.
The force was so strong; it compelled me to say everything.
I went blank. It was as if something in me came up.
I started manifesting. I didn’t know what was happening
but I noticed that I was blank and I felt something was burning me.
From my head to my toes, I was on fire.
That was what if felt like.
All glory be to God Almighty, ever since I was delivered
I have been able to sleep well like a baby, without taking drugs.
I have been able to eat well.
Even the pain I had in this knee for almost four years - I didn't know what caused the pain -
went instantly when the Wise Man touched my leg.
I no longer feel the pain.
I can now kick my leg and stretch it to any limit and I don’t feel any pain.
I said “wow”- this is really the touch of God on my life.
The craving that I had disappeared.
The voice I heard, I no longer hear it.
Rather, I hear a good and gentle voice telling me what to do, say and how to act.
You mean to say, brother, that since your deliverance,
you have not gone anywhere near drugs, cigarettes, or alcohol.
Yes, since my deliverance I have never dreamt of or had any urge for drugs or alcohol,
I have not even thought about it.
The thought of it doesn’t come to me at all.
It is as if the Holy Spirit sealed the gate so that anything not of God cannot come in.
I was so delighted. I kept on praying for that gate to continue to be sealed from now on till I die.
When I open the Bible, it is as if the Bible is talking to me,
it’s giving me guidelines on how to move, giving me steps to take.
I make sure that I have a notebook with me because every second
Words of God keep coming through the Prophet.
I hear words that inspire me that tell me how to fortify myself
to reach out to the youth out there and tell them how to avoid those devices
and to tell them how to protect themselves from those devices.
That is what the Word of God has been doing to me.
Viewers all around the world, I have this message for you.
We are Christians, meaning Christ-like.
Jesus Christ came; He was humble and loyal to His Father.
He did not partake in things that concern the flesh.
So, if you want to make it to Heaven, avoid things that concern the flesh -
the spirit of lust, alcoholism, seduction, everything, please do not go into it,
even drugs – these are the food of the enemy, the devil.
It is not from God; Jesus Christ was not a drug addict.
He was not a smoker, He was not a drinker, He was not a womaniser.
Please, avoid those things, for they give the devil access to you. Thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.